[{"id": 2294, "question": "Recreational tree climbing is taking root in the ecotourism industry, and it's sending guys like Tim Kovar to far off reaches of the globe. Kovar, a tree-climbing instructor, recently returned to the U.S. from Brazil, where he spent time developing a tree-climbing operation thanks to the \"slow travel\" movement. Slow travel, is like the slow food movement, the practice of giving fast food in favor of homegrown cooking--the kind that takes hours to prepare and enjoy. Likewise, slow travel urges visitors to experience a place's natural surroundings and learn about the ecology in a way not afforded by extreme games. \"Tree climbing is a slow activity,\" says Kovar. \"It's not something you do quickly and then you're on to the next thing or event.\" There is no such thing as a quick climb, especial...\n\nQ: What's the best title for the passage?", "options": ["Tree-climbing travelling", "Slow travel movements", "Dangers of climbing", "Respect for nature"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1342, "question": "Once a general manager wanted to test his people, who had come from all over India, about their values of life. He announced that in their folders , there is PVC pouch and in it there is a seed. When they return, they must put the seed in a pot with good soil and look after it very well. He would hold a competition at the next year's seminar and the best plants would be awarded suitably. Everyone did what was told to him. A year passed quickly. And the next year in a big hall, what a great scene! There were hundreds of pots and a great variety of plants-all except one. In this pot was soil, but no plant! The owner of the pot was standing quietly and feeling ashamed of himself. The general manager called him on the stage. He asked him what happened and he told him the truth. He planted the ...\n\nQ: The author wanted to tell us the importance of  _  by writing this passage.", "options": ["being careful", "being honest", "knowing how to plant", "knowing how to please the manager"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2975, "question": "Most Americans receive at least two or three credit card applications in the mail every month.Why have credit cards become so popular? For a merchant, the answer is obvious.By putting charge slips in a bank, the merchant can change credit card sales into cash.In return for processing the merchant's credit card transactions , the bank charges a fee that ranges between 1.5 and 5 percent. The easiest way to establish credit is to open checking and savings accounts at your local bank.Then apply for a gasoline or store credit card.These cards are fairly easy to get because retailers want you to buy their goods and services.The third step, and the most dangerous one, is obtaining a major credit card like Visa, MasterCard, or American Express. It is important to choose a credit card carefully bec...\n\nQ: If you don't pay off the credit card debts in full each month, the best way to save money is to   _  .", "options": ["stop using the credit card", "apply for a card with the lowest interest rate", "apply for more credit cards", "explain your problems to your creditors"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 955, "question": "The Jungle Book Lost in the jungles of India as a child and adopted into a family of wolves, Mowgli is brought up on a diet of Jungle Law, loyalty, and fresh meat from the kill. Regular adventures with his friends and enemies in the jungles improve this child's strength and cleverness and stir every reader's imagination. Price: $ 7.79 ISBN-13: 978-1613820742 Average Customer Review: A Stolen Life The first work of its kind--Jaycee Dugard's personal life story, her own story of being kidnapped in 1991. When Jaycee was eleven years old, she was kidnapped from a school bus stop. She was missing for more than eighteen years, and gave birth to two daughters during her imprisonment . Price: $ 19.79 ISBN-13: 978-1442344983 Average Customer Review: While We're Far Apart Five-time Christy Award win...\n\nQ: If you are interested in personal life stories, then you can choose the book   _  .", "options": ["A Stolen Life", "The Jungle Book", "The Fashion Police", "While We're Far Apart"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 189, "question": "Boys' schools are the perfect place to teach young men to express their emotions and involve them in activities such as art, dance and music. Far from the traditional image of a culture of aggressive masculinity ,the absence of girls gives boys the chance to develop without pressure to be consistent to a stereotype ,a US study says. Boys at single-sex schools were said to be more likely to get involved in cultural and artistic activities that helped develop their abilities to express their emotions,rather than feeling they had to obey to the\"boy code\"of hiding their emotions to be a\"real man\". The findings of the study are against the received wisdom that boys do better when taught alongside girls. Tony Little,headmaster of Eton,warned that boys were being ignored by the British education ...\n\nQ: It is commonly believed that in a mixed school boys  _  .", "options": ["perform ly better", "grow up more healthily", "behave more responsibly", "receive a better education"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 649, "question": "I was dirty smelly hungry and some somewhere beneath all that, suntanned .It was the end of an Inter-Rail holiday.My body couldn't take any more punishment. My mind couldn't deal with any more foreign timetables, currencies or languages. \" _ ,\" I said, as I stepped onto home ground.I said exactly the same thing the following year.And the next, all I had to do was buy one train ticket and, because I was under twenty--five years old,I could spend a whole month going anywhere I wanted in Europe. Ordinary beds are never the same once you've learnt to sleep, in the passage of a train, the rhythm rocking you into a deep sleep. Carrying all your possessions on your back in a tucksack makes you have a vefy basic approach to travel,and encourages incredible wastefulness that can lead to burning soc...\n\nQ: What the writer liked about traveling without his parents was that", "options": ["he could see more interesting places", "he could spend more time sightseeing", "he could stay away from home longer", "he could make his own decisions"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1441, "question": "I'm usually fairly skeptical about any research that concludes that people are either happier or unhappier or more or less certain of themselves than they were 50 years ago. While any of these statements might be true, they are practically impossible to prove scientifically. Still, I was struck by a report which concluded that today's children are significantly more anxious than children in the 1950s. In fact, the analysis showed, normal children aged 9 to 17 exhibit a higher level of anxiety today than children who were treated for mental illness 50 years ago. Why are America's kids so stressed? The report cites two main causes: increasing physical isolation brought on by high divorce rates and less involvement in community, among other things and a growing perception that the world is a ...\n\nQ: The first and most important thing parents should do to help their children is  _  .", "options": ["to lower their expectations for them", "to set a good model for them to follow", "to get them more involved socially", "to improve them with a safer environment"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3188, "question": "Dreaming is a natural part of who we are. We explore our dreams and develop personal dreams. We even like to dream BIG! For the most part our dreams and wishes focus on the end result. We see ourselves in love, married, driving a great car, on vacation, with tons of money, in a great career, etc. Dreaming about the end result is just fantasizing and wishing. Wishing relies on some magical force to make our dreams turn into reality, and we become unhappy as we're not living our dreams. So how can we make our dreams come true? That is a question we all often struggle with. Even though we struggle with the answer, the answer is not that clear. We make our dreams come true with the action we take. In my opinion, if you dream about being in good health, then change your dream to see yourself wo...\n\nQ: If you want to keep fit,  _", "options": ["you'd better dream a sweet dream first.", "you must love the process of the journey.", "you would rather begin with your diet and exercise.", "you should have a good beginning first."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 747, "question": "We do not know when man first began to use salt, but we do know that it has been used in many different ways throughout history. Historical evidence shows, for example, that people who lived over 3,000 years ago ate salted fish. Thousands of years ago in Egypt, salt was used to preserve the dead. Stealing salt was considered a major crime during some periods of history. In the eighteenth century, for example, if a person was caught stealing salt, he could be put in prison and his ears could be cut off. In the Roman Empire, one of the most important roads was the one that carried salt from the salt mines to Rome. Guards were stationed along the route to protect against salt thieves, and they received their pay in salt, thus bringing the English word, salary. Any guard who fell asleep while ...\n\nQ: According to the text, salt can be used in the following EXCEPT   _  .", "options": ["keeping dead bodies", "punishing thieves", "protecting crops", "making industrial products"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 92, "question": "According to Andrew, it never would have happened if he had not had a flat tire on Highway 10 last night at about 7:30. He was on his way to attend a three-day sales meeting when he had the flat. tyre. Unfortunately, he did not have a spare, so he pushed the car off the road, locked it up, and managed to thumb a ride back to Pine Grove. It was after eleven o'clock when he finally got home, and it was then that his real problems started. When Andrew left home at about 5:30, he had told his wife not to expect him back until Thursday or Friday. Knowing that his wife was nervous about staying in the house alone at night, Andrew took the precaution of checking all the windows in the house to be sure they were locked, so that he could report to his wife that the house was secure. He convinced hi...\n\nQ: As Andrew had a flat tyre on the way, he  _  .", "options": ["had to take another car to attend the meeting", "rode on a bike to attend the meating", "asked for a lift to go back home", "borrowed a car to go back home"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2046, "question": "When a child is told he is \"uncool\", it can be very painful. He may say he doesn't care, and even act in ways that are opposite of cool on purpose. But ultimately, these are simply ways to handle sadness by pretending it's not there. Helping a child feel better in school had to be careful. If you say, \"Why are you worried about what other children think about you? It doesn't matter!\" Children know that it does matter. Instead, an active way may be best. You could say, \"I'm going to do a couple of things for you to help you feel better in school.\" If a boy is having trouble making friends, the teacher can help him. The teacher can arrange things so that he has chances to use his abilities to contribute to class projects. This is how the other children learn how to value his good qualities a...\n\nQ: Which of the following is TRUE?", "options": ["Children don't care others' comments on them.", "It's only teacher's work to make children popular.", "Parents should take their children out for picnic and shows more often.", "Inviting children's friends to family activities is good for them to make friends."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2253, "question": "After months of fear, hate and prosecution , the music and consumer-electronics industry decided to try to make beautiful music together. Last week the Secure Digital Music Initiative, a combination of 100 music, electronics and high-tech companies announced that it agreed on a music format known as MP3 which caused disagreement. Nowadays, more and more young people are fond of music that is played on their portable MP3 players. So this announcement attracted a lot of attention in both the producer and consumer sides. MP3 allows the digital music in CDs to be made smaller to a tenth its size and still sounds great. MP3 songs are small enough to be traded online; they are made by the millions to the _ of record companies, which fear that everything ever released on disc will end up online f...\n\nQ: According to the passage, what is NOT an advantage of the MP3 format?", "options": ["The size of music can be shortened to one tenth of its original size.", "The fans can enjoy the music before the formal release of the music.", "The new musicians can enter the industry more easily.", "The struggle against piracy will be proved difficult."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2576, "question": "Have you ever heard the saying \" _ \"? Here is how a new teacher made friends with the girls and boys in her class on the first day of school. As the bell rang, the teacher smiled at each girl and boy. Then she said in a quiet voice, \"Good morning. How nice it is to have all of you in my class this year. I'd like to know each of you. I am sure we will enjoy working together.\" Everyone felt that she meant what she said because of her sweet voice and her friendly look. She told the girls and boys her name and wrote it on the blackboard. Then she told them some of the things she liked to do and she was hoping to do with them during the year. Then she said to the class, \"Now you know my name and the things I like and I want to know your names and the things you like. Then I will feel that I kno...\n\nQ: If you want to make friends with others, which of the following shouldn't you do?", "options": ["Learn more about them.", "Go on journeys together.", "Find out your differences.", "Try to be the same as them."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1365, "question": "Tom appeared on the sidewalk with a bucket of whitewash and a long-handled brush. He stopped by the fence in front of the house where he lived with his aunt Polly. He looked at it, and all joy left him. The fence was long and high. He put the brush into the whitewash and moved it along the top of the fence. He repeated the operation. He felt he could not continue and sat down. He knew that his friends would arrive soon with all kinds of interesting plans for the day. They would walk past him and laugh. They would make jokes about his having to work on a beautiful summer Saturday. The thought burned him like fire. He put his hand into his pockets and took out all that he owned. Perhaps he could find some way to pay someone to do the whitewashing for him. But there was nothing of value in hi...\n\nQ: Tom was about to agree to let Ben whitewash when he changed his mind because   _  .", "options": ["Tom wanted to do the whitewashing by himself", "Tom was afraid Ben would do the whitewashing better.", "Tom was unwilling to let Ben do the whitewashing", "Tom planned to make Ben give up his apple first"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3309, "question": "It is amazing to note that the Internet is still such a new device, and yet it is one of the fastest and most powerful media tools. But think about it for a moment. On the Internet, a big online company can be run by two guys out of their garage. So it is only reasonable that people shopping on the Net would be a little _ of the security levels. Internet giants such as Microsoft knew consumer confidence was the key to getting virtual shopping off the ground, and they work hard to make people feel safe to shop online. Credit card companies, too, quickly saw the potential for Internet shopping, and have installed things like online shopping insurance for people. If you ever have a problem with your online credit purchases, many credit card companies will happily refund your money and then se...\n\nQ: _  leads to consumers' trust in online shopping.", "options": ["Shopping law", "Shopping convenience", "Internet access", "Shopping security"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1835, "question": "Experts have put forward detailed plans for a tunnel to connect Taiwan with the Chinese mainland. The shortest proposed route would be 126 kilometers more than twice the length of the English Channel Tunnel. And the longest proposed route would be 207 kilometers. A recent conference in Xiamen, Fujian Province brought together more than 70 experts. The event was co-sponsored by universities from Taiwan and the Chinese mainland. Fujian is the province where both proposed routes would begin. There is direct passenger access between the mainland and Taiwan by air and sea at the moment. Experts say that it is better to start research sooner rather than later, although there is a lack of government funding . There are no technical problems to build a Taiwan tunnel. But it will require an improve...\n\nQ: Which is the longest tunnel in the world at present?", "options": ["The tunnel between Lyon and Turin.", "The English Channel Tunnel.", "The Taiwan Straits tunnel.", "The passage doesn't mention it."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1243, "question": "When my friend went to Europe last summer, instead of snapping photographs of the Louvre or the Eiffel Tower or Stonehenge, she brought back 32 rolls of ... cathedral ceilings. Ceilings. For the 10 years I've known her I had never suspected that she was this passionate about stained glass. Still one of the best things about such pictures -- despite their obvious narrow appeal -- is that they can't help but tell us a great deal about the people who took them. So I shouldn't have been surprised when I got the roll of film back from my 5-year-old son's first camping trip. I opened the envelope, naively expecting to see pictures of the nightly campfire, the sun setting over the forest, and possibly even a deer or two. Instead, I saw an off-center picture of tennis shoes. Not even his tennis sh...\n\nQ: The author changed her mind on her son's picture taking because  _   .", "options": ["her friend persuaded her to do so", "her son's pictures finally struck her", "she realized the truth by herself inspired by the surrounding examples", "it suddenly occurred to her that she herself had also taken unique pictures before"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3342, "question": "People with disabilities make up a large part of the population. It is estimated that over 35 million Americans have physical, mental, or other disabilities. About half of these disabilities are \"developmental\", i.e., they occur before the individual's twenty-second birthday, often from genetic conditions, and are severe enough to affect three or more areas of development, such as mobility, communication, employment, etc. Most other disabilities are considered \"adventitious\", i.e., accidental or caused by outside forces. Prior to the 20th century, only a small percentage of people with disabilities survived for long. Medical treatment for these disabilities was unavailable. Advancements in medicine and social services have created a climate in which people with disabilities can expect to h...\n\nQ: A \"developmental\" disability   _  .", "options": ["develops very slowly over time", "is caused by forces", "occurs in youth and affects development", "is getting more and more severe"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 425, "question": "Do you love holidays but hate gaining weight? You are not alone. Holidays are times for celebrating. Many people are worried about their weight. With proper planning, though, it is possible to keep normal weight during the holidays. The idea is to enjoy the holidays but not to eat too much. You don't have to turn away from the foods that you enjoy. Here are some tips for preventing weight gain and maintaining physical fitness: Don't skip meals. Before you leave home, have a small, low-fat meal or snack . This may help to avoid getting too excited before delicious foods. Control the amount of food. Use a small plate that may encourage you to \"load up \". You should be most comfortable eating an amount of food about the size of your fist . Begin with soup and fruit or vegetables. Fill up befo...\n\nQ: What is the best title of the passage?", "options": ["How to avoid holiday feasting.", "Do's and don'ts for keeping slim and fit.", "How to avoid weight gain over holidays.", "Wonderful holidays, boring experiences."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 793, "question": "In my living room, there is a plaque that advises me to \"Bloom where you are planted.\" It reminds me of Dorothy. I got to know Dorothy in the early 1980s, when I was teaching Early Childhood Development through a program with Union College in Barbourville, Kentucky. The job responsibilities requested occasional visits to the classroom of each teacher in the program. Dorothy stands out in my memory as one who \"bloomed\" in her remote area. Dorothy taught in a school In Harlan County, Kentucky, Appalachian Mountain area. To get to her school from the town of Harlan, I followed a road winding around the mountain. In the eight-mile journey, I crossed the same railroad track five times, giving the possibility of getting caught by the same train five times. Rather than feeling excited by this dri...\n\nQ: What does the author mainly intend to tell us?", "options": ["Whatever you do, you must do it carefully.", "Whoever you are, you deserve equal treatment.", "However poor you are, you have the right to education,", "Wherever you are, you can accomplish your achievement."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 695, "question": "Jenny went to visit her friends in New York last weekend.Her friends met her at the airport on Friday afternoon and drove her to the hotel.They had dinner at a Chinese restaurant and went to see a film after that. Jenny and her friends set out early on Saturday morning for a farm and stayed there until Sunday morning.During their stay, they went fishing and swimming in the small river on the farm.They played football in the field and enjoyed a big meal around a camp fire , singing and dancing till late into the night. Nobody could get up early on Sunday morning.So when they got back to New York City, it was about three o'clock in the afternoon.They drove right to the airport because Jenny didn't want to miss her plane back home.Jenny only stayed in New York for two nights but she had a gre...\n\nQ: When did Jenny go back home?", "options": ["On Saturday afternoon.", "On Sunday morning.", "On Saturday evening.", "On Sunday afternoon."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1436, "question": "Life is full of sweet surprises for Chinese pop singer Edell. She majored in design in a Canadian college. But when she was looking for a job after graduation, she found herself rising as a star in singing. Then she became a hostess on TV. \"These are roles I never expected to take,\" she said. Edell is open to every possibility in life, not afraid to try new things. She says that every day she tries to get herself ready to take any chance that occurs in life. \"My mom told me chance only rewards those with a prepared mind,\" she said. \"So I've tried to explore my potential talents. Thus I won't be at a loss when the right opportunity comes up.\" Edell learned ballet in her childhood until she broke her back in practice. She then fell in love with music. Like many girls of her age, she has a ri...\n\nQ: What does the underline word \"It\" refer to?", "options": ["Studying the English biography hard.", "The 91-page English biography.", "The ceremony of the Asian MTV Awards.", "The MTV channel."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2200, "question": "Medicine comes in lots of different packages. Painkillers in a tablet can make your headache go away. Antibiotic cream from a tube can prevent your cuts from becoming infected. But can medicine come packaged in chicken eggs? A team of scientists from Scotland say \"yes\". They've engineered special chickens that lay eggs with disease-treating drugs inside. These eggs come from chickens that have been engineered to produce certain drugs inside their egg whites. These drugs are made of molecules called proteins . Animals make thousands of proteins -- they're the main element in skin, hair, milk and meat. Since animals can make proteins easily, they're good candidates for making protein drugs. Researchers have already made cows, sheep and goats produce protein drugs in their milk. But chickens ...\n\nQ: The best title for the passage is   _  .", "options": ["Chicken Eggs to Replace Medicine", "Chicken Eggs as Drug", "Chicken Eggs and Medicine", "Chicken Eggs and Animal Milk"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2529, "question": "Scientists are using a kind of eye-tracking equipment to learn how babies look at the world. In the lab, children 5 months and older crawl and walk up, down and over adjustable wooden slopes , gaps and steps. It may seem like the set for a new reality television show, but there are no prizes, except perhaps for the researchers. They hope to understand what makes one child respond to another, how babies adjust their look to their hands and feet to handle objects, and how these very young children adapt to changes. The findings provided by these eye-trackers suggest that babies may be more capable of understanding and acting on what they see than had been thought. \"Quick looks at their mothers' faces may be all they need to get the information they want. They seem to be surprisingly efficien...\n\nQ: What does Dr. Adolph think of the result of the research?", "options": ["Exciting.", "Unacceptable.", "Strange.", "Surprising."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 180, "question": "School education is very important and useful. Yet no one can learn everything from school. A teacher, no matter how much he knows, he can not teach his students everything they want to know. The teacher's job is to show his students how to learn. He teaches them how to read and how to think. So much more is to be learned outside school by the students themselves. It is always more important to know how to study by oneself than to learn some facts or a formula by heart. It is actually quite easy to learn a certain fact in history or a formula in mathematics. But it is very difficult to use a formula in working out a maths problem. Great scientist, such as Einstein, Newton and Galileo, didn't get everything from school. But they were all so successful and invented so many things for men. Th...\n\nQ: The main reason for the success of the great scientists is that  _  .", "options": ["the teachers who had taught them were all experienced.", "they used to work and study without a moment's rest.", "they had received more schooling than other people", "they know how to study and worked hard"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 50, "question": "\"What is the most important thing you've done in your life?\" The question was put to me during a presentation I gave to a group of lawyers. The answer came to me in an instant. It's not the one I gave, because the situation was not right. As a lawyer in the entertainment industry, I knew the audience wanted to hear some amusing stories about my work with well-known people, but here's the true answer: The most important thing I've ever done occurred on October 8,1990. I began the day playing tennis with an old friend I hadn't seen for a while. Between points we talked about what had been happening in each other's lives. He and his wife had just had a baby boy, who was keeping them up at night. While we were playing, a car came screaming up the road toward the courts. It was my friend's fath...\n\nQ: When he was asked about the most important thing he had done in life at a presentation, the author    _   .", "options": ["felt it was not an interesting question", "thought for a while and spoke his mind", "gave an answer from a lawyer's point of view", "didn't give the real answer"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2868, "question": "Be Healthy! Be Slim! Be Beautiful! Discover the secret for a Healthy, Slim, Beautiful You! Discover how to be Healthy, Slim and Beautiful! I love this healthy diet program because it helps you lose weight, lose inches, feel healthy and look beautiful. This healthy diet is an 8-week program which is unlike other diet regimes because it focuses on proper nutritional first and weight loss second. Your body must have proper levels of minerals, vitamins, and protein in order to work well. It provides a simply lifestyle change to give you more energy and improve your health most greatly. It offers control over stomach and continuing hunger with a calorie dense diet allowing 1,700 to 2,000 calories a day. If a person has a weight problem their body probably is not working at proper levels of basi...\n\nQ: If you \"Click Here\", what will you read on the Internet?", "options": ["Some other programs.", "The content of this program.", "Some interesting foods.", "Some products you can buy."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 548, "question": "Introductory Chemistry was taught at Duke University for many years by Professor Bonk.One year, two guys took the class and did pretty well on all the quizzes and midterms.They each had a solid A.These two friends were so confident in going into the final that the weekend before the final week, despite the Chemistry final being on Monday, they decided to go to the prefix = st1 /UniversityofVirginiato party with some friends. They had a great time there.However, with their hangovers and tiredness, they overslept all day Sunday and didn't make it back to Duke until early Monday morning.Rather than taking the final then, they found Professor Bonk after the final and explained to him how they missed the final.They told him they went up to the University of Virginia for the weekend and had plan...\n\nQ: After the final, the two guys would probably   _  .", "options": ["apologize to Professor Bonk", "get the same high marks", "lose interest in their Chemistry", "feel happy and relieved"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1246, "question": "Billy's favorite color is orange. But he can't see what orange looks like. Billy is blind. A month after he was born, his mother noticed that his eyes weren't quite as big as a normal baby's.\"Billy would never be able to see.\" the doctor told his mother. After that Billy's mother began talking to him, describing things she saw outside the window. She described everything to him. Billy does not only depend on his mother's descriptions to learn about the world around him. He sees with his ears and his hands, too. He has perfect hearing. When people make phone calls, he can tell the numbers they dial . Billy loves computer science. He began teaching himself computer programming when he was just seven years old. His dream school would be Stanford University. He gets top grades in his classes, ...\n\nQ: How did Billy's mother help him?", "options": ["By teaching him how to draw.", "By asking teacher for advice.", "By describing everything to him.", "By sending him to his dream school."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1157, "question": "What does the future hold for the problem of housing? A good deal depends, of course, on the meaning of \"future\". If one is thinking in terms of science fiction and the space age, it is at least possible to assume that man will have solved such trivial and earthly problems as housing. Writers of science fiction, from H.G. Wells onwards, have had little to say on the subject. They have conveyed the suggestion that men will live in great comfort, with every imaginable apparatus to make life smooth, healthy and easy, if not happy. But they have not said what his house will be made of. Perhaps some new building material, as yet unimagined, will have been discovered or invented at least. One may be certain that bricks and mortar(,) will long have gone out of fashion. But the problems of the nex...\n\nQ: The writer believes that the biggest problem likely to confront the world before the end of the century   _  .", "options": ["is difficult to foresee.", "will be how to provide enough houses in the hottest parts of the world.", "will be how to feed the ever growing population.", "is the question of finding enough ground space."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1780, "question": "Shoplifting is happening in stores or supermarkets throughout the world. However, shoplifting happens more in British stores, according to a recent research, by the UK-based Center for Retail Research. Napoleon once considered prefix = st1 /Britainas \"a nation of shopkeepers\", to which so many people dreamed of traveling. Now it seems it is a nation of shoplifters. According to the research,Britainis the most light-fingered country in Europe, with nearly one in every two cases of shoplifting across the continent taking place in British stores. The report said there were nearly 566,000 reported cases of shoplifting inBritainout of a Europe-wide total of 1.27 million. The next worst countries in Europe,FranceandGermany, came well belowBritainwith only 188,000 and 167,000 cases, respectively....\n\nQ: From what Joshua Bamfield said, it can be inferred that   _  .", "options": ["it's the highest level of criminality that caused Britain's social problem", "Britain's social problem of shop theft came from varieties of sides", "Britain's poor showing does not lie wholly at the doorstep of Britons", "it's traveling groups of thieves that make up the majority of Britain's shoplifters"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1124, "question": "Father's Garden My father was always a good gardener. One of my earliest memories is standing without shoes in the freshly tilled soil, my hands blackened from digging in the ground. As a child, I loved following Dad around in the garden. I remember Dad pushing the tiller ahead in perfectly straight lines. Dad loved growing all sorts of things: yellow and green onions, watermelons almost as big as me, rows of yellow corn, and our favorite--- red tomatoes. As I grew into a teenager, I didn't get so excited about gardening with Dad. Instead of magical land of possibility, it had turned into some kind of prison. As Dad grew older, his love for gardening never disappeared. After all the kids were grown and had started families of their own, Dad turned to gardening like never before. Even when ...\n\nQ: Why did the author like the garden when he was a child?", "options": ["He wanted to be a garden-crazy like his father.", "He loved being in the garden with his father.", "The garden was full of his favorite food.", "The garden was just freshly tilled."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 195, "question": "Oliver Radtke believes Chinglish mistranslations may be fun, but are not to be made fun of. \"My message on Chinglish is: It should be conserved . It shouldn't be treated as a cheap joke for foreign tourists to laugh at but as a cultural treasure,\" said the 32-year-old multimedia designer, who frequently visited China for almost a decade before moving to Beijing in 2007. \"I'm trying to challenge the idea that there is only one type of standard English -- the English that's spoken in America or in the British Isles -- which is shortsighted, because Chinglish is already being used by millions of people to communicate with one another.\" So, since 2005, he has collected more than 5,000 examples of \"the wonderful results of an English dictionary meeting Chinese grammar\" on his website www.chingl...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements does Radtke agree with?", "options": ["Chinglish will gradually disappear as years go by.", "Chinglish is invented to amuse foreign tourists.", "Chinglish will be treated as a cultural treasure.", "Chinglish is actually a variety of English."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2100, "question": "Expressions about water are almost as common as water itself. The expressionto be in hot water is a very old expression. Hot water was used five hundred years ago to mean being in trouble. One story says it got that meaning from the custom of throwing extremely hot water down on enemies attacking a castle. That no longer happens. But we still get in hot water. When we are in hot water, we are in trouble. It can be any kind of trouble--serious or not so serious. A person who breaks a law can be in hot water with the police. A young boy can be in hot water with his mother, if he walks in the house with dirty shoes. Beingin deep wateris almost the same as being in hot water. When you are in deep water, you are in a difficult position. To keep your head above wateris a colorful expression that...\n\nQ: What can you say to your friend Jane, who is troubled by a mistake she has made?", "options": ["Keep your head above water.", "Throw cold water.", "It is water over the dam.", "It can hold water."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1450, "question": "When I was 16 years old and in foster care in Tennessee, people told me I was unadoptable. But I desperately wanted a family. I sought the help of a judge, even the commissioner of the Department of Children's Services, and was adopted just a week before my 18th birthday. We have a lot to be grateful for and this holiday season let's not forget about the more than 415,000 youth in foster care especially older youth. These youth are the most likely to get overlooked for adoption, but they shouldn't be. They need and deserve a family just as much as young children do. Making an older youth a part of your family can bring just as much a joy as adopting a baby or a younger child--without all the diapers and potty training. My adoption was life changing and probably the best thing that ever hap...\n\nQ: What's the author's main purpose of writing the passage", "options": ["To express her appreciation for her family.", "To show sympathy to the unadoptable older youth.", "To appeal to more people to adopt the older youth.", "To persuade the readers not to believe others' words."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2188, "question": "Recently a committee of the National Academy of Sciences inprefix = st1 /Washingtonreleased a report .It confirmed that world temperatures increased about six-tenths of a degree Celsius in the last one hundred years. The report also confirmed evidence that the level of carbon dioxide in increasing. The best information about climate in the past comes from tests of ice many kilometers deep in Antarctica and Greenland .These tests show that levels of carbon dioxide today are the highest ever measured .These findings have led scientists to believe that carbon dioxide is a major cause of climate warming. Carbon dioxide is released into the atmosphere when fuel is burned. Oil ,coal and wood are all fuels that release the gas .When biological waste breaks down ,it also releases carbon dioxide. H...\n\nQ: Which one is NOT mentioned in this passage that can be the source of carbon dioxide?", "options": ["Oil", "Trees", "Wood", "Soil"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3416, "question": "I am a professor of sports and exercise so I often deal with nervousness in my research with sports people. Actually, most people experience nervousness at some time or another. If you are feeling anxious, my advice is to first find the cause or causes. Make a list of those things that are making you nervous and work out which ones you can do something about. Focus all of your efforts on managing the causes that you can control. Most people cannot tell the difference between controllable and uncontrollable causes, so things they can't control become a big reason for nervousness. Dealing with this is very important if people want to keep a healthy mind. Simply try to accept the uncontrollable causes of nervousness. You might be worried about the weather on a big day, an accident or an attac...\n\nQ: The writer thinks there is no use worrying about some causes of nervousness because_.", "options": ["most are not very important", "they are not the real causes of the problem", "they cannot be controlled by people", "it's better to deal with one cause at a time"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1281, "question": "When looking for love, people may go to some extreme lengths. They might go on blind dates set up by family and friends. They might write personal ad to place in newspapers. Or they might use a computer to help them in their search for a soul mate by joining an online dating service. Some people have even tried to find their perfect match through game shows on television. Many of these TV dating shows, including The Bachelor andWho Wants to Marry Multimillionaire?, have proved to be popular, with millions of viewers watching each week to find out which of the contestants will find true love. Of all these game shows, perhaps the one with the most unexpected ending was Mr. Right, which was shown in England in 2002. On the show, a bachelor, thirty-five-year-old Lance Gerrard-Wright, dated fif...\n\nQ: What is this passage mainly about?", "options": ["how a famous couple met and got married", "the best way to meet a husband or wife", "why the show Mr. Right was a big hit", "how to act on a date with a stranger"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2648, "question": "Collections were the inspiration for a project at Thomas Tallis School, which formed part of the Imagine Children's Literature Festival last autumn. Each child (aged 12-13) beatified a box and wrote a story on the subject of collections to throw inside it. The boxes were spread within the Royal Festival Hall's Ballroom. Some were left empty to encourage The subject chosen by Luren was an imaginative one. \"It's a sort o f Cinderella story,\" she told me, inspired by a collection of letters from her cousin, ha the story these become love letters, burned by a creel stepmother. Lauren's best friend Charlotte is the stepmother. \"I'm in Charlotte's story too,\" says Lauren, \"and I get run over.\" Charlotte's tale was inspired by the girls' coin collection. \"We've collected foreign coins for years -...\n\nQ: What were the children asked to do in the project?", "options": ["To meet friends at Thomas Tallis School", "To write stories on the subject of collections.", "To encourage visitors to write their own stories.", "To have their friends for characters in the stories."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 972, "question": "Do you scream on a roller coaster ride? You slowly climb up a steep slope until an almost vertical drop, and then... Ahhhhhhhh! Thrill-seekers like me are in luck because theme parks are pushing the boundaries of technology to create the fastest, tallest, scariest roller coasters the world has ever known. Alton Towers in Britain opened the world's first 14-1oop roller coaster a few months ago, called The Smiler. Over in Abu Dhabi, Ferrari World claims to have the world's fastest one. Ferrari World's Formula Rossa ride sends out passengers from 0-240km/h in just 4. 9 seconds. During this rapid acceleration they experience G-forces only fighter pilots usually feel: Up to 4. 8G. The designer of several rides at Alton Towers, said: \"While we can stand 6-8Gs for very short periods of time, ff w...\n\nQ: We can learn from the passage that   _", "options": ["all the theme parks are creating the fast roller coasters", "the Smiler sends out passengers from 0-240km/h in just 4.9 seconds", "it is unusual for fighter pilots to feel up to 4.8G", "the more the money is spent, the faster the roller coaster can go"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1538, "question": "When I left my bag on a train, I lost my most precious possession, a small framed photograph of my great grandparents, Emily and Gordon Baker. The frame was made of silver, with an elegant flower design in one corner. The photograph was taken in March 1939 on their wedding day. Emily looked very happy, and Gordon looked rather alarmed. A few months later, he was killed in action in North Africa. I received the photograph when my aunt Mabel died. I'm a student at Edinburgh University and I live in an old Edwardian house. At the end of last term, I packed a large bag and a small bag and set off for London, where I was planning to catch the Eurostar train to Paris. Minutes after getting off the train at Kings Cross Station, I realized that I'd left the small bag in the overhead luggage rack. ...\n\nQ: The man advertising the frame proved it was the author's   _    .", "options": ["by calling the seller up immediately", "according to the price of the silver frame", "by the author's explanation about the photo", "by the date written on the back of the photo"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2983, "question": "Family Vs Technology Modern technology certainly changes family behavior, but does it really damage family life as many people fear? Not necessarily, says Dr. Silva, a professor in Sociology at the Open University, she also argues it is wrong to assume technology erodes(,) the quality of family life. \"There is the idea that technology has an influence on the family and the family suffers. My take is quite different,\" she explains. \"Technological change happens because people's lives change. And it is people's choices of how to live that creates processes of innovation as well. The family has a role like the economy or like technology itself in changing the world. The imagination is important in driving the things technologists want to find for our daily lives. People desire to see nature a...\n\nQ: What can we learn from the passage?", "options": ["The microwave oven was first used by working mothers.", "People cook less because of modern kitchen equipment.", "Technology has little effect on the changes of family behavior.", "People need less skill to do housework due to advanced technology."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3423, "question": "Hello-Hello, a creative mobile language learning company, announced the launch of Hello-Hello World, a free application for the iPad that helps people learn a new language by connecting them with native speakers through social networking. The application lets users complete language lessons and connect with Hello-Hello's global community of language learners with members in almost 100 countries to help each other in the learning process. Hello-Hello World is available in 11 different languages and allows users to submit both oral and writing exercises for their friends and Hello-Hello's language experts to review. Users are also able to provide written feedback on their friend's exercises directly from their mobile devices. \"The most effective way to learn a new language is through total i...\n\nQ: It is implied in the passage that   _  .", "options": ["there is a potential market for this mobile technology", "mobile technology is being used for classroom learning", "students do not know how mobile technology can be used", "it is difficult for Hello-Hello to change the mobile industry"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3253, "question": "Teachers and textbooks _ -- your future could be under threat from a quickly developing and very smart technology. University of California researchers led by Jacob White hill recently programmed teaching robots to react to facial expression. Whitehill's achievement marked a major step forward in the way people could one day learn by establishing facial expression recognition in robot teachers. The teaching robots or, Intelligent Tutoring Systems (ITS) are computer systems that provide personalized instruction and feedback to students without human intervention. The facial expression recognition allows a computer to react according to expressions a user makes. He said that the system was an important development in improving learning systems. \"Classical ITS typically have a somewhat rigid ...\n\nQ: The newly teaching robots are more advanced because they have  _", "options": ["Jacob Whitehill as the designer", "a program reacting to facial expressions", "a system to help people learn", "a set of instruments to recognize your voice"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 198, "question": "We produce 500 billion of plastic bags in a year worldwide and they are thrown away polluting oceans, killing wildlife and getting dumped in landfills where they take up to 1000 years to decompose. Researchers have been unsuccessfully looking for a solution. The 16-year old Canadian high school student, Daniel Burd, from Waterloo Collegiate Institute, has discovered a way to make plastic bags degrade in as few as 3 months, a finding that won him first prize at the Canada-Wide Science Fair, a $10 000 prize, a $20 000 scholarship, and a chance to revolutionize a major environmental issue. Burd's strategy was simple: Since plastic does eventually degrade, it must be eaten by microorganisms . If those microorganisms could be identified, we could put them to work eating the plastic much faster ...\n\nQ: Daniel Burd won first prize at the Canada-Wide Science Fair because  _  .", "options": ["he found a new kind of microorganism", "he contributed much to environmental protection", "he found a way to degrade plastics in shorter time", "he could encourage microbes growth in an easier way"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 343, "question": "John Blanchard stood up from the bench, straightened his Army uniform, and studied the crowd of people making their way through Grand Central Station. He looked for the girl whose heart he knew, but whose face he didn't, the girl with the rose. His interest in her had begun thirteen months before in a Florida library. Taking a book off the shelf he found himself intrigued, not with the words of the book, but with the notes penciled in the margin. The soft handwriting reflected a thoughtful soul and insightful mind. In the front of the book, he discovered the previous owner's name, Miss Hollis Maynell. With time and effort he located her address. She lived in New York City. He wrote her a letter introducing himself and inviting her to correspond. The next day he was shipped overseas for ser...\n\nQ: Which of the following can be the best title for the passage?", "options": ["A Test of Love", "The Symbol of Rose", "Love is blind", "Don't Judge a Book by its Cover"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1955, "question": "Talking plants might sound like characters in a fairy tale. But recent scientific studies have shown that plants communicate with each other and with other living things in a surprising number of ways. To understand them, scientists say, we just have to learn their language. Farmers are especially interested in what plants have to say. \"Plants are able to communicate with all sorts of organisms . They can communicate with giant bacteria, with other plants and with insects. They do this chemically,\" said Cahill, an Ecology Professor of the University of Alberta in Canada. Plant scientists are just beginning to understand this chemical \"language\". Cahill says studies have shown, for example, that plants can evaluate conditions in their immediate environment and take appropriate actions. Plan...\n\nQ: Which would be the best title for the passage?", "options": ["Communication between Plants", "A Chemical \"Language\"", "Plants Can Talk", "How Plants Protect Themselves"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1306, "question": "To a large degree, the measure of our peace of mind is determined by how much we are able to live in the present moment. Regardless of what happened yesterday or last year, and what may or may not happen tomorrow, the present moment is where you are -- always! We allow past problems and future concerns to control our present moments, so much that we end up anxious, frustrated, depressed, and hopeless. We often convince ourselves future will be better than today. John Lennon once said, \"Life is what's happening while we're busy making other plans. \"When we're busy making other plans\", our children are busy growing up, the people we love are moving away and dying, our bodies are getting out of shape, and our dreams are slipping away. In short, we miss out on life. Many people live as if life...\n\nQ: It implies  from the passage that   _  .", "options": ["many people know how to fight against fear", "it isn't necessary to fear for future", "you can gain more happiness by putting off your pleasure", "some people make plans for their children to improve their lives"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1998, "question": "One silly question I simply can't understand is \"How do you feel?\" Usually the question I asked of a man's action--a man on the go, walking along the street or busily working at his desk. So what do you expect him to say? He'll probably say, \"Fine, I'm all right, \" but you've put a bug in his ear--maybe now he's not sure. If you are a good friend, you may have seen something in his face, or his walk, that he overlooked that morning. It starts him worrying a little. First thing you know, he looks in a mirror to see if everything is all right, while you go merrily on your way asking someone else. \"How do you feel?\" Every question has its time and place. It's perfectly acceptable, for example, to ask \"How do you feel?\" if you're visiting a close friend in hospital. But if the fellow is walkin...\n\nQ: The question \"How do you feel?\" seems to be correct and suitable when asked of   _  .", "options": ["a man working at his desk", "a person having lost a close friend", "a stranger who looks worried", "a friend who is ill"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 557, "question": "EDGEWOOD-Every morning at Dixie Heights High School, customers pour into a special experiment: the district's first coffee shop run mostly by students with special learning needs. Well before classes start, students and teachers order Lattes, Cappuccinos and Hot Chocolates. Then, during the first period, teachers call in orders on their room phones, and students make deliveries. By closing time at 9.20 a.m., the shop usually sells 90 drinks. \"Whoever made the chi tea, Ms. Schatzman says it was good,\" Christy McKinley, a second year student, announced recently, after hanging up with the teacher. The shop is called the Dixie PIT, which stands for Power in Transition. Although some of the students are not disabled, many are, and the PIT helps them prepare for life after high school. They lear...\n\nQ: How did Christy McKinley know Ms. Schatzman's opinion of the chi tea?", "options": ["She met her in the shop.", "She heard her telling others.", "She talked to her on the phone.", "She went to her office to deliver the tea."], "answer": 2}]